A Guide to the University of Virginia Office of the Vice President for Business and Finance Office Administrative Files, 1909, [1953]-1980
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Vice-President for Business and Finance, 1979-1980
  - Heritage Repertory Theatre, 1979-1980 (Box 12)
  - Hospital, 1979-1980 (Box 12)
  - Information Services, 1979-1980 (Box 12)
  - Institutional Analysis Office, 1979-1980 (Box 12)
  - Internal Auditor, 1979-1980 (Box 12)
  - Legal Advisor, 1978-1980 (Box 12)
  - Law, 1979-1980 (Box 12)
  - Library, 1979-1980 (Box 12)
  - McIntire School of Commerce, 1979-1980 (Box 12)
  - Medicine, School of, 1979-1980 (Box 12)
  - Miller, Burkett White Center for Public Affairs, 1979-1980, 2 folders. (Box 12)
  - Mortgage Loans, Approved Applications, 1979-1980 (Box 12)
  - Mortgage Loans, Faculty, 1979-1980 (Box 12)
  - NACUBO, 1979-1980 (Box 12)
  - Newcomb Hall Bookstore, 1979-1980 (Box 12)
  - Parking and Transit, 1979-1980 (Box 12)
  - Patent Foundation, 1979-1980 (Box 12)
  - Personnel (Graded Pay Scale), 1979-1980 (Box 12)
  - Personnel Office, 1979-1980 (Box 12)
  - Personnel Training Programs, 1979-1980 (Box 12)
  - Planning, Department of, 1979-1980 (Box 12)
  - Pratt, John Lee Estate, 1976-1980 (Box 12)
  - President, 1979-1980 (Box 12)
  - Price, Waterhouse and Co., 1979-1980 (Box 12)
  - Price, Waterhouse and Co., Management Letters, 1979-1980 (Box 12)
  - Provost, 1979-1980 (Box 12)
  - Purchasing Agent, 1979-1980 (Box 12)
  - Property, ESAB Building, 1976-1980 (Box 12)
  - Property, State Farm Building, 1977-1980 (Box 13)
  - Research Policy Council, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
  - Residential Housing and Subsidiary Services, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
  - Retirement Plans, VSRS, TIAA, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
  - Risk Management and Safety, Department of, 1978-1980 (Box 13)
  - Scholarships and Fellowships, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
  - Space Administrator, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
  - Speech and Drama, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
  - Student Affairs, Vice-President for, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
  - Student Council, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
  - Summer Quarter, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
  - Telephone System Financing, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
  - Treasurer, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
  - University Comptroller, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
  - University Printing Office, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
  - Visiting Committee (Personnel), 1979-1980 (Box 13)
- Vice-President for Business and Finance, State Office Files, A-Z
  - Administration and Finance, Secretary of, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
  - Attorney General, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
  - CSSBO, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
  - Comptroller, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
  - Department of Health, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
  - Department of Highways, 1977-1980 (Box 13)
  - Division of Engineering and Buildings, 1970-1980 (Box 13)
  - Education, Secretary of, 1979-1980, 2 folders. (Box 13)
  - General Services, Department of, 1978-1980 (Box 13)
  - Governor, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
  - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
  - Management Analysis and Systems Development, Department of, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
  - Manpower Utilization Policies and Procedures, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
  - Personnel and Training, Division of, 1972-1980 (Box 13)
  - Planning and Budget, Division of, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
  - Purchases and Supply, Division of, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
  - Sponsored Porgrams, Office of, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
  - Student Accounts Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
  - State Council of Higher Education, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
  - SCHEV, Finance Advisory Committee, 1978-1980 (Box 13)
  - State Librarian, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
  - Taxation, Department of, 1978-1980 (Box 13)
  - Treasurer, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
  - Treasurer, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
  - Virginia Community Colleges, 1978-1980 (Box 13)
  - Virginia Supplemental Retirement System, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
- Restricted Files (Box 14)